Civil Service Employees Association, Inc. (CSEA), American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Local 1000 Records apap015
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Civil Service Employees Association, Inc. (CSEA), American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) Local 1000 Records
1918-2015
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap015
64.26 cubic ft. 2868 Digital Files
This collection documents the day-to-day activities of the Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA) from 1918 to the present. There is no documentation of the organization's initial years of existence, but significant material about administration, meetings, membership, agreements, publications, and organizational history.
Access
Access to this record group is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
All microfilm items in this manuscript group (with the exception of the Meeting Transcripts which were microfilmed by CSEA) were lent to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department Special Collections and Archives, by the Civil Service Employees Association, Inc. (CSEA), AFSCME Local 1000, and subsequently microfilmed as a part of the Harry Van Arsdale, Jr., Labor History Project. The originals were returned to CSEA. All other records are donated to the University Libraries on aregular basis.
Biographical History
The Civil Service Employees Association, Inc., or CSEA, is the largest public employees' union in New York State with over 265,000 members. CSEA began in Albany, New York in 1910 as a collective effort by a small group of state employees to secure better wages and working conditions. Originally known as the Association of State Civil Service Employees, the organization adopted its current name in November 1946. Between 1920 and 1940 the organization grew from a handful of workers to a membership of over 600. This increase in membership was largely based upon the admittance of non-competitive class civil service employees. By 1947 the organization admitted another class of state employees, local government workers, with the issuance of a charter to Westchester County employees.
Ever-increasing membership prompted CSEA's leadership to formalize the union. As part of this effort, CSEA purchased its first building in 1947. Along with the procurement of an organizational headquarters and the statewide issuance of charters, CSEA also published a constitution. As expressed in the CSEA constitution, the fundamental purpose of the organization is to "represent its workers with respect to all terms and conditions of employment, to uphold and extend the principles of merit and fitness in public employment, and to maintain and promote efficiency in public service and to advance the interests of all Civil Service employees."
CSEA's commitment to its members encouraged other state employees to join the union. CSEA's membership expanded to more than 40,000 by 1948. While other labor organizations discontinued operations in times of economic hardship, CSEA's membership remained active. By the 1960s the organization had become so large in number and effective that its endorsement became much sought after in the New York State political arena.
In 1967 the Taylor Law went into effect, changing the face of labor relations in New York. The Taylor Law established "good faith" collective bargaining practices for both management and labor. Furthermore, it declared all strikes by state employees illegal and prescribed a "two for one" penalty for those labor organizations whose members participated in a strike. In spite of the Taylor Law and its prohibitions against strikes by state employees, at midnight on March 31, 1972, New York State employees engaged in their first strike. The striking workers, members of CSEA, walked off their jobs to protest meager wage increases presented during contract negotiations. The strike lasted two days and resulted in contracts which included salary increases and productivity bonuses.
In 1974 CSEA "regionalized" creating six geographic subdivisions in New York. The regions are: 1) Long Island, serving Nassau and Suffolk Counties; 2) Metropolitan, serving New York City; 3) Southern, serving the seven counties of the mid-Hudson area; 4) Capital, serving the 14 counties surrounding Albany; 5) Central, serving 20 counties with Syracuse at the hub; and 6) Western, serving 14 counties extending to Buffalo and the westernmost part of the state.
In 1978 CSEA undertook a trial affiliation with the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) as Local 1000. CSEA became a permanent member of AFSCME in 1981. Currently, CSEA is the largest affiliate of AFSCME, which in turn is the largest member of the AFL-CIO.
CSEA publishes an official monthly newspaper for its members. Originally entitled The Civil Service Leader, CSEA changed the publication's name in 1978 to The Public Sector, and to The Work Force in 1998. The newspaper serves to keep members informed of the union's activities locally and statewide.
During its 100 year history, CSEA has achieved significant accomplishments. In 1920 CSEA had its first victory with the establishment of the New York State Retirement System. Throughout the 1930s, CSEA became more influential in state politics. In 1931 CSEA introduced a legislative measure that led to the 1936 abolition of the 72-hour work week for employees of state institutions. Another accomplishment of the 1930s was the passage of the Feld-Hamilton law on June 3, 1937. The new law set in place a salary plan that provided state employees with minimum salaries and equal pay for equal work. As the decade of the 1940s approached, CSEA took on a new direction. 1946 set the stage for enormous growth with the official change of the organization's name to CSEA and the constitutional change that opened up membership to all New York public employees. Throughout the 1960s, 1970s, and 1980s, CSEA was a very influential labor union. CSEA backed the 1967 Public Employees Fair Employment Act, also known as the Taylor Law. CSEA also had a large role in the passage of the Public Employment Safety and Health Act. The new law created safer workplaces for all public employees by creating minimum safety standards. In the late 1970s, CSEA made its most dramatic move as a labor organization when it joined AFSCME. A major success of the 1980s was CSEA's constitutional change to allow the organization of private sector employees. As CSEA approached and entered the new millennium, it realized that it would be faced with new challenges as it advocated for workers' rights, including a growing pool of retirees. After several years of fighting for a permanent cost of living adjustment (COLA) to the pension system, CSEA utilized the union's influential power to obtain the benefit in 2000. Today CSEA continues to serve as an advocate for workers, bargaining for just contracts and campaigning for quality and affordable health care, education, safe workplaces, and guaranteed Social Security benefits.
Following is a list of CSEA Presidents from the organization's founding through today:
William M. Thomas, 1910-1918
Wellington D. Ives, 1920-1921
Major Philip G. Rosa, 1921-1922
Dr. James I Wyer Jr., 1922-1923
Dr. Horatio M. Pollack, 1923-1925
Danial Chase, 1925-1926
James A. Cromie, 1926-1927
Robert B. Haner, 1927-1928
William C. Smith, 1928-1929
William F. McDonough, 1929-1934
Beulah Bailey Thull, 1934-1935
Dr. Charles A. Brind Jr. 1935-1941
Harold J. Fisher, 1941-1944
Clifford C. Shoro, 1944-1945
Dr. Frank L. Tolman, 1945-1950
Jesse B. McFarland, 1950-1953
John F. Powers, 1953-1959
Joseph F. Feilly, 1959-1967
Dr. Theodore Wenzl, 1967-1977
William C. McGowan, 1977-1988
Joe McDermott, 1988-1994
Danny Donohue, 1994-2019 Mary Sullivan, 2019-present
Scope and Contents
The records of the Civil Service Employees Association span from 1918 to the present. There is no documentation of the organization's initial years of existence. The records include Meetings, Records of Resolution or Motion, Legal and Administrative Files, Subject Files, Publications, News Clippings, Press Releases, Audio Visuals, Scrapbooks, records of the CSEA 100 Project, an extensive interview project created to help celebrate the union's centennial in 2010, Photographs, and Membership. Of these, publications is the largest series and includes CSEA's official newspapers The Civil Service Leader, The Public Sector, and The Work Force. Please note that the records of the Capital City Council of the Civil Service Association, which formed in 1918, are also included in Series 1, Subseries 1: Board of Directors Meetings.
The collection contains a variety of record formats. A selection of early to mid-twentieth century meeting transcripts and publications are housed on microfilm, some filmed by CSEA and others by the M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives. There is a substantial number of paper files including correspondence, newspapers, meeting and interview transcripts (also digitized), meeting minutes, and subject files, and both hard copy and digitized publications and photographs. In addition, there are video and audio tapes and scrapbooks. There are a small number of born digital materials.
Conspicuously absent from the collection is any documentation of the strike in 1972 by CSEA members, except for any discussions in the minutes and transcripts of meetings. While only lasting two days, it is noted in New York labor history for being the first strike by state employees under the Taylor Law of 1967, which made it illegal for New York State employees to strike and imposed harsh financial penalties for those who did.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is organized into the following series: Series 1: Meetings; Subseries 1.1: Board of Directors Meetings, 1918-2015; Subseries 1.2: Annual Delegate Meetings, 1947-2014; Subseries 1.3: State Executive Committee Meetings, 1971-1983; Subseries 1.4: County Executive Committee Meetings, 1948-1983; Subseries 1.5: Meetings of State Chapter Presidents, 1971-1982; Subseries1.6: Meetings of County Delegates, 1976; Series 2: Records of Resolution or Motion, 1961-1966; Series 3: Legal and Administrative Files, 1977-2014, Undated; Series 4: Subject Files, 1964-2011, Undated; Series 5: CSEA Publications, 1932-2014; Series 6: News Clippings, 1980-2013, Undated; Series 7: CSEA Communications, 1971-2017, Undated; Series 8: Audio Visual, 1960-2013, Undated; Series 9: CSEA 100 Project, 1998-2009; Series 10: Images, 1970-2010, Undated; Series 11: Scrapbooks, 1958-1971; Series 12: Membership, 1939-2015, Undated. Series 1-7 and 11 are arranged chronologically. Series 9-10 and 12 are alphabetical. Series 8 is arranged alphabetically by format and then chronologically within the format.
Series 1 - Meetings, 1976
Subseries 1.1: Board of Directors Meetings
Subseries 1.2: Annual Delegate Meetings
Subseries 1.3: State Executive Committee Meetings
Subseries 1.4: County Executive Committee Meetings
Subseries 1.5: Meetings of State Chapter Presidents
Subseries 1.6: Meetings of County Delegates
Series 2 - Records of Resolution or Motion, 1961-1966
Series 3 - Legal and Administrative Files, 1977-2014
Series 4 - Subject Files, 1964-2011
Series 5 - CSEA Publications, 1932-2014
Series 6 - News Clippings, 1980-2013
Series 7 - CSEA Communications, 1971-2015
Series 8 - Audio Visual, 1960-2013
Series 9 - CSEA 100 Project, 1998-2009
Series 10 - Images, 1970-2010
Series 11 - Scrapbooks, 1958-1971
Series 12 - Membership, 1939-2015
Civil service--New York (State); Government employee unions--New York (State); Labor laws and legislation--New York (State); Minutes; Newspapers; Photographs; Files by subject; Transcripts; Oral histories (document genre); Digital Files; Civil Service Employees Association (N.Y.)
- Meetings, 1918-2015; 1; 8.3 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series is divided into six subseries to reflect the meeting type.
  - Board of Directors Meetings, 1918-2015; 1.1; 4.70 cubic ft.
    This series consists of reels containing annual meeting minutes (with tables of contents), correspondence, CSEA President's reports, and verbatim transcripts of Board of Directors, County and State Delegate, and State Executive Committee meetings. Also contained on Reel 10 are the minutes of special delegates meetings and the records of the Capital City Council of the Civil Service Association which formed in 1918. The series also includes Board of Director Meeting files related to the quarterly Board meetings. These files feature committee reports, memorandums, state officer reports, interim Board of Directors meeting materials, and meeting minutes.
    CSEA filmed all reels in this series. Please note that many pages are difficult to read.
    - Transcripts of Meetings, 1918-1946 (Reel 10)
    - Transcripts of Meetings, 1933 March 7-1955 July 28 (Reel 1)
    - Transcripts of Meetings, 1953-1957 October 28 (Reel 2)
    - Transcripts of Meetings, 1960 October-1965 June (Reel 3)
    - Transcripts of Meetings, 1965 August 19-1968 August 1 (Reel 4)
    - Transcripts of Meetings, 1968 August 1-1971 May 18 (Reel 5)
    - Transcripts of Meetings, 1971 June 13-1974 October 5 (Reel 6)
    - Transcripts of Meetings, 1973 October 24-1976 February 28 (Reel 7)
    - Transcripts of Meetings, 1976 February 12-1977 November 6 (Reel 8)
    - Transcripts of Meetings, 1978 January 12-1979 October 21 (Reel 9)
    - Transcripts of Meetings, 1979 November 29-1979 December 2 (Reel 10)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (1 of 2), 1971 (Box 1 (1-Meetings), Folder 1)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (2 of 2), 1971 (Box 1 (1-Meetings), Folder 2)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1978; 1981; 1983 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 1)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1995 January 25 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 2)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1995 June 2 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 3)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1995 August 24 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (1 of 2), 1996 January 11 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 5)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (2 of 2), 1996 January 11 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1996 March 7 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1996 May 15 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1996 August 15 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 9)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (1 of 2), 1996 October 31 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 10)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (2 of 2), 1996 October 31 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 11)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1997 January 9 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 12)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1997 February (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 13)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1997 March 6 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 14)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1997 April 24 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 15)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1997 June 19 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 16)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1997 August 27 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 17)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1997 October 23 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 18)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1998 January 8 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 19)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1998 March 19 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 20)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1998 May 28 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 21)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1998 July 23 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 22)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1998 September 16 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 23)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1998 November 19 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 24)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1999 January 14 (Box 2 (1-Meetings), Folder 25)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (1 of 2), 1999 April 22 (Box 3 (1-Meetings), Folder 1)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (2 of 2), 1999 April 22 (Box 3 (1-Meetings), Folder 2)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1999 July 29 (Box 3 (1-Meetings), Folder 3)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 1999 November 17 (Box 3 (1-Meetings), Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2000 January 13 (Box 3 (1-Meetings), Folder 5)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2000 April 14 (Box 3 (1-Meetings), Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2000 July 13 (Box 3 (1-Meetings), Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2000 November 9 (Box 3 (1-Meetings), Folder 8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2001 January 18 (Box 3 (1-Meetings), Folder 9)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2001 April 26 (Box 3 (1-Meetings), Folder 10)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (1 of 2), 2001 July 12 (Box 3 (1-Meetings), Folder 11)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (2 of 2), 2001 July 12 (Box 3 (1-Meetings), Folder 12)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2001 September 20 (Box 3 (1-Meetings), Folder 13)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2001 November 29 (Box 3 (1-Meetings), Folder 14)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2002 January 17 (Box 3 (1-Meetings), Folder 15)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2002 April 4 (Box 3 (1-Meetings), Folder 16)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2002 July 18 (Box 3 (1-Meetings), Folder 17)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2002 October 1 (Box 3 (1-Meetings), Folder 18)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2003 January 16 (Box 3 (1-Meetings), Folder 19)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (1 of 2), 2003 April 10 (Box 3 (1-Meetings), Folder 20)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (2 of 2), 2003 April 10 (Box 3 (1-Meetings), Folder 21)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2003 July 10 (Box 3 (1-Meetings), Folder 22)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2003 September 19 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 1)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2003 November 14 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 2)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (1 of 2), 2004 January 15 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 3)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (2 of 2), 2004 January 15 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2004 February 27 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 5)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2004 April 15 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2004 May 28 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2004 July 8 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2004 November 12 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 9)
    - Interim Board of Directors Reports, 2005 March 11 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 10)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2005 April 28 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 11)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2005 June 27 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 12)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2005 August 5 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 13)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (1 of 2), 2005 September 13 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 14)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (2 of 2), 2005 September 13 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 15)
    - Interim Board of Directors Report, 2005 November 18 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 16)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (1 of 2), 2006 January 12 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 17)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (2 of 2), 2006 January 12 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 18)
    - Interim Board of Directors Report, 2006 March 3 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 19)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2006 April 20 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 20)
    - Interim Board of Directors Report, 2006 June 2 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 21)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2006 July 13 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 22)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2006 September 14 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 23)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2007 January 11 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 24)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2007 April 12 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 25)
    - Interim Board of Directors Report, 2007 June 1 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 26)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2007 July 26 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 27)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2007 September 27 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 28)
    - Interim Board of Directors Report, 2007 November 30 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 29)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2008 January 10 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 30)
    - Interim Board of Directors Meeting, 2008 Febraury 25 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 31)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2008 April 17 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 32)
    - Interim Board of Directors Report, 2008 May 30 (Box 4 (1-Meetings), Folder 33)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2008 July 10 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 1)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2008 September 11 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 2)
    - Interim Board of Directors Report, 2008 November 21 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 3)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2009 January 15 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 4)
    - Interim Board of Directors Report, 2009 February 20 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 5)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2009 April 16 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2009 July 30 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2009 September 10 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (1 of 2), 2010 January 14 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 9)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (2 of 2), 2010 January 14 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 10)
    - Interim Board of Directors Reports, 2010 March 1 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 11)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (1 of 2), 2010 April 29 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 12)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (2 of 2), 2010 April 29 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 13)
    - Interim Board of Directors Reports, 2010 June 1 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 14)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2010 July 15 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 15)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (1 of 2), 2010 September 30 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 16)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (2 of 2), 2010 September 30 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 17)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2011 January 20 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 18)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2011 April 14 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 19)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2011 July 21 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 20)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2011 September 22 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 21)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (1 of 2), 2012 January 12 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 22)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (2 of 2), 2012 January 12 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 23)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2012 April 12 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 24)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2012 July 12 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 25)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2012 September 28 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 26)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2013 January 17 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 27)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2013 April 10 (Box 5 (1-Meetings), Folder 28)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2013 July 10 (Box 6 (1-Meetings), Folder 1)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2013 September 26 (Box 6 (1-Meetings), Folder 2)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2014 January 16 (Box 6 (1-Meetings), Folder 3)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2014 April 10 (Box 6 (1-Meetings), Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2014 July 31 (Box 6 (1-Meetings), Folder 5)
    - Interim Board of Directors Reports, 2014 November (Box 6 (1-Meetings), Folder 6)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2014 September 12 (Box 6 (1-Meetings), Folder 7)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2015 January 15 (Box 6 (1-Meetings), Folder 8)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (1 of 2), 2015 April 23 (Box 7 (1-Meetings), Folder 1)
    - Board of Directors Meeting (2 of 2), 2015 April 23 (Box 7 (1-Meetings), Folder 2)
    - Board of Directors Meeting, 2015 July 16 (Box 7 (1-Meetings), Folder 3)
  - Annual Delegate Meetings, 1947-2014; 1.2; 1.8 cubic ft.